[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to urban legends that spread in 1997, people in this country began pumping air from a bicycle pump into their rectum resulting in their explosion.", "correct_answer": "Thailand", "incorrect_answers": ["The United States", "Poland", "South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What marrow produces blood cells in the human body?", "correct_answer": "Red marrow", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue marrow", "Yellow marrow", "Green marrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term cheiromancy, also known as palm reading, is derived from Greek. What does it literally mean?", "correct_answer": "Hand divination", "incorrect_answers": ["Secrets of the hand", "Fortune telling", "Skin testing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Monticello, meaning small mountain in Italian, is the name of an estate near Charlottesville, Virginia, which belonged to which US President?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "incorrect_answers": ["George", "James Madison", "John Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Octopi live alone all their lives except when mating.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The chemical symbol of Fluorine is Fl.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the film Cape Fear released?", "correct_answer": "1991", "incorrect_answers": ["1987", "1993", "1989"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What conic section is used to describe electromagnetic waves?", "correct_answer": "Parabolas", "incorrect_answers": ["Points", "Lines", "Ellipses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An LCD monitor with a DVI or VGA connector can be connected to a laptop computer with the same connectors, as a second monitor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The symbol for the chemical element iron is this.", "correct_answer": "Fe", "incorrect_answers": ["I", "Zn", "Br"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the fourth US president?", "correct_answer": "James Madison", "incorrect_answers": ["James Monroe", "John Quincy Adams", "Thomas Jefferson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People suffreing from this mental illness manifest a psychiatric condition as a physical complaint.", "correct_answer": "Somatization Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Agoraphobia", "Kleptomania", "Munchausen Syndrome"]}]